City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Engineering Department, 1949-1986; 3; 12 cubic ft.
  - Urban Renewal Developers, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal Disposition Parcel 5B and 3B High St, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal East Newburgh Project NYR 189A, 1966-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Eastside, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Eastside, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Eastside 189, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Engineering Charges, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal Engineering Contracts, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Engineering Department Contracts, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal Gordon Marvel, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal Housing and Urban Development HUD 6220, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal Industrial Site, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal Industrial Site, 1965-1970; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Lake Street Rehabilitation, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal Meetings, 1966-1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal Meetings, 1968; 1973-1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Meetings, 1968-1969; 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Meetings, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal Meetings, 1976-1977; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal Misc. Correspondence, 1964-1976; Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Montgomery Street, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal NYM 10 Demo Contr #2, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Urban Renewal NYR 12 Demol Contr #10, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal NYR 12 Demolition Contr. #11, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal NYR 12 Water St Program Status Report Aug '66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal NYR 189 Demol Contr No. 2 Included Palatine Hotel, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal NYR 189 Project Improvements, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demol. Contr. #7, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demol. Contr. #8, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demol. Contr. No. 3, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demol. Contr. No. 5, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demolition Contr. #12, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demolition Contr. #12, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-12 Demolition Contr. #13 1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal NYR-189 Demolition Contr. No. 1, 1966-1970; Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal Parcel #12 Lake St., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal Plan for the East Newburgh Urban Renewal Project, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal Proj. NY R-18, 1972; Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal, Rosen, David, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal Second Street, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal Smith Street, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal Street Improvements, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal Street Improvements, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal Street Improvements Work File (1 of 2), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal Street Improvements Work File (2 of 2), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal Technical Guides, 1955-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal Workable Program, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Weekly Meetings, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Workable Program, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Zoning Map, Record Copy, 1966 (Box 7, Item 39)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of City of Newburgh, Undated (Box 7, Item 40)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Ann St., Broadway, Lake St., Undated (Box 7, Item 41)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Carpenter Ave., City Terr., Robinson Ave., Undated (Box 7, Item 42)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Bridge St., Carson Ave., Mill St., Undated (Box 7, Item 43)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Chambers St., Gidney St., Liberty St., South St., Undated (Box 7, Item 44)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Cottage Ave., Robinson Ave., North St., North Plank Rd., Undated (Box 7, Item 45)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of DuPont Ave., Fowler, Undated (Box 7, Item 46)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Gidney Ave., Fullerton, Gedney Way, Leicht Pl. - includes economic, 1965 (Box 7, Item 47)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Liberty St., South St. Area, Undated (Box 7, Item 48)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Monument St., Henry St., Beacon St., So. Lander St., Bay View - includes economic and proposed school, Undated (Box 7, Item 49)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of South St. - includes economic, 1965 (Box 7, Item 50)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of South St., West St. Area, Undated (Box 7, Item 51)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map of Wisner, Broadway - includes economic, 1965 (Box 7, Item 52)
  - Zoning/Re-Zoning Map with Notes, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Item 53)
  - Zoning Variances Map, Undated (Box 7, Item 54)
- Administrative, 1945-2000; 1
  Series includes various types of administrative files from the Urban Renewal project of the 1960s and 1970s. These include mainly business correspondence but also Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency materials, reports, contracts, payment ledgers, relocation payments, deeds, meeting minutes, and newspaper articles.
  - 100-102 Grand NYR 189, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 105-107 Smith, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 108 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 11 Hudson View Terrace, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - 110 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 111 Chambers Street, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 111 Chambers Street Newburgh NY County of Orange, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - 112 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1-1-2, 9 Washington Pl, Lot 21, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - 114 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 116 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 118 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 120 Water Street- Levinson, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 122 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 124 and 126 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 128 Liberty Street, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - 128 Liberty Street Specifications for Rehabilitation Sue Schweitzer, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - 128 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 128 Third Street House Copy (Not SHPO), 1980 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - 130 Carson Avenue, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - 130 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 132 Montgomery, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 143 Washington St, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - 147 Grand Street, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - 151 Lander Street Field Review Only, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 161 Chamber Street, Newburgh, NY 12550, Undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 167 Dupont Avenue, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 176 Montgomery Street, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 180 Montgomery Detailed Rehab Proposal, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 189 Expend Budget, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - 19 Edward Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 19 Forsyth Place, Specified Work List and Rehabilitation, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - 1967 HUD Financial Report and Open Audit Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - 1969 Survey and Planning Budget, 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - 1972-1973 Minutes (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 1st Year Closeout, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 203 Robinson Ave., 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 21 Edward Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 2-1-2 High Street Lot 10, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - 22 Edward Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 233-234 Water, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 238 Grand St: Carey Improvement Specs for Urban Renewal 1960s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 24 South Water Street, 1970-1971; 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 24 South Water Street Lot 51, 1969-1970; 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 241 Third Street, Newburgh NY, Owner Billy Williams, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 242 Water Street Mamie Smith, 1962; 1964 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - 2-4-2, Clinton Square Lot 39, 1970; 1974-1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 25 Hawthorne Avenue, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - 254 Montgomery St, Rehab Application, 4-2-1, 1962-1966; 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2-5-5, 69 Second Street, Lot 33, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - 262 Van Ness Street, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - 269 Grand Street, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - 279 Grand Street Rehab Specifications, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 2nd Amendatory Contract NYSUR 100, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - 3 Johnes Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 3-1-1, Deed in Progress, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 3-1-12, 148-150 Water St., Lot 1-2, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - 3-1-2, Deeds in Progress, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 3-1-3, Deeds in Progress, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 3-1-8, Deeds in Progress, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 339 Water Street Lot 26, 1971-1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 34 Lander Street (Yellow), 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - 35 Johnes Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 38 Edward Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 3rd Quarter of 1973 Sewer Rents and Water Rents (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 3rd Year Contract Funding Agreement, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - 3rd Yr Closeout, 1972; 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - 41 Johnes Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 4-1-4, 194 Water Street Woodrow W. Wansley, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 4-2-1 Parcels 45-61, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - 49-59 Washington Terrace Herman Zaransky and Luke Stein, 1970-1976; 1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - 4th Quarter of 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 50 Fifth Street, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 51 Carpenter Street, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - 52 Fifth Street, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 55 Overlook Place General Standards for Property Rehabilitation, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - 57 Lander Street, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - 59 Van Ness Street, Undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - 61 Chamber Street, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - 67 Lander Street, 1980-1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - 67-69 South St., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 69 Lander Street, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - 701 HUD Special Contract, NYR 189 Contract, HUD Letter of Consent, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - 71 South, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 74 Lander Street Specifications, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - 77-79 Broadway, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 8/10 South Miller Street Prepared by Dwelling Group, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 81 Courtney Avenue, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 81 Courtney Avenue Newburgh NY County of Orange, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - 85 William Street Specified Work List and Rehabilitation Standards, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - 9-11 Hasbrouck Street, Undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - 93 Dubois Street, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - 93-103 Grand- Mandel NYR 189, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 96-98 Grand NYR 189, 1983; Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 97-103 Grand, 77-79 Broadway, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 98 Grand Hazards, 1958; 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - 99 Smith St, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - A Plan and Action Program, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - A.C.C. American City Corporation, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - A.C.C. Contract, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - A831-A886 January 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - A887-A953 February 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - A954-A1026 March 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Abalene Pest Control, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - ABY Equipment Rental Inc, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Acceptance of Deeds by City, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Ace Hydraulic and Equipment Service, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Acquisition of Rehabilitation Properties, 1971-1975; Undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Acquisition of Urban Renewal Disposition Parcels, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Acquisition of Urban Renewal Disposition Parcels, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Acquisition of Waterfront Properties, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Acquisition Prices Requests for HUD Concurrence, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Acute Enterprises, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Additional Relocation, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Adjustments and Vouchers, 1970-1973; 1991 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Administrative Budget 1967-1974, 1970-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Advertising 83.11E, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Affidavit of Service, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Affirmative Action Program, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Agency and Air Survey Corp, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Agency Meeting 1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Agency Meeting 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Al Atkins and Al's Smoke Shop Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Al Atkins Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1961; 1966 (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Al Atkins, Water St., BBQ, Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1963; 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - AL Santagada, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Alan Lascher, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Alarm Broadway School, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Alex Finkel, Gold Platter Bar Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Algie Faulkner Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - All Incoming Calls, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - All Nations Church, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Allan Kuslansky, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Allan Miller and Florian Fischler, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Allen, John, 149 Water Street, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Allen's Tobacco Store 149 Water Street, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Al's Billiard Parlor, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Alton Faison Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Amendatory Application for Loan and Grant 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Amendatory Contract NYSUR-19 Copy 1, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - American City Corporation, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - American Institute of Architects Standard Form of Agreement, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Anna Mincey Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - Anna Ray, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Anne Haber Book #2, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Anne Haber Book #3, 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Anne Haber Book #4, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Anne Haber Book #5, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Anne Haber Book #6, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Anne Haber Book #7, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Anne Haber Book #8, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Annie Mincey 114 Smith Street, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report 1971, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report for 1968, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Anthony Minard Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Appellate Division Rules Orange County, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Application and Loan Grant, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Appraisal Report and Valuation Analysis as of August 11, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Appraisal Reports 1981-1990, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Appraisal: Water Street Renewal Project, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appraisals Processing of Forward History Summary, 1971; 1973 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Approved Contractors- Walden NY Community Development Program, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Approved HUD 6144 NYR 189 Acquisition Concurrence on Prices, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - April 29, 1994 103 Liberty Street Newburgh NY 12550 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Architect's Project Number 119, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Argenio Brothers, Inc., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Argenio Brothers, Inc. Pt. 2, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Arlether Mills Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Arthur and Betty Wilson, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Arthur Miller, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Arthur Wynkoop Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1961-1965 (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Arties General Store, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Artko Wrecking Co., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Audit File, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Audit Proposals, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Audit Report Urban Renewal Program, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Audit Report Urban Renewal Program Jan 1, 1977 to Oct 31, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Audits 1971-1975, 1968; 1970-1975 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - August 10, 1970 Spiral Notebook (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Aurelia Miller 171 Water Street, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Aurelia Miller Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Authorization for Rent Refund, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Bakery, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Bard Chevrolet, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Bard Chevrolet, 11-23 Wash. Terrace, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Bard Chevrolet, 68 Lake St, Lot 21, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Barnes and Smith v Tarrytown and Newburgh, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Barton Building Co. Inc, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Beatrice E Fisher, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Benjamin Walker Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bernice Oates Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bernice Oates Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1964 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Berry, Jane 252 VanNess St., 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Bertram Gold, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Best Church 80-82 Montgomery Street, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Bet Ros Realty Corporation, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bid Invitations and HUD Handbook, 1975; 1980 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Bid Invitations, Deposition Parcels, NYR-189, 1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bid Tabulation, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Bids, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bids and Proposals, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Bids on Receipts and Register, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Bids Received 129 and 150 Lander Street, 1981-1983; Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Bill's Express, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Binder V Application for Loan and Grant, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Bishop's Service Inc, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Black Binder Unnamed, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Blake and Associates Inc, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Blanket Condemnation, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Block 3-2-5 Lot 44 Arthur and Hattie Holden, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Blooming Grove Equipment Corp, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Board of Education, 1965; 1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Bob's Lunch, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Boice Wheeler, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Boice Wheeler Pt 2, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Borden Dental Lab, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Brian D Thompson, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Brian Donovan Thompson, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - The Bridge Fund Westchester, 1992-1995 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Brown Binder Unnamed, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bucci NYA 10 Parcels 7 and 8, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Budget FY 88, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Budget Papers- NYA 10, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Budget R-150 Surveyor Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Building Information, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Burch, Wilfred H, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Buxton General Contractor, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - By-Laws NURA, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - C. Miller Grocery, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Caldonia Ellis, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Candeub, Flessig, and Associates, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Carstens, Iannaccone, Associates, LTD to 159 Grand Street, Undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Cash Grant-in-Aid, NYR-189, 1970-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cash Reimbursements 1 of 2, 1968-1972 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Cash Reimbursements 2 of 2, 1967-1971 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Casill Martin Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Cassie Struthers Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Catherine Brown, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Celia Zelsburg, 1960; 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Center Median or Mall-Lake Street, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cerone Place Apartments Newburgh, New York, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Cerone Place License Agreements, Erie Lackawanna Railroad, 1972-1974; 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Certified Mail Code Compliance Department, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chapman and Pesetsky, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Charge Verification- Grant, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Charge Verification- Loan, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Charles A McMellon, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Charles A. Gibson, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Charles E. Taylor 53 Water Street Relocation Payment, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Chazen Associates, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Chestnut Partners, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Chestnut Partners- Limited Partnership Ad, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - City Attorney Opinions 1970 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - City Council, 1970-1973; 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - City Council Special Meet, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - City Engineer, 1964; 1967; 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - City Manager, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - City Manager 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - City Manager 1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - City of Newburgh Accompanying Exhibits Workable Program 1966, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - City of Newburgh Acquisition Appraisals Comparable Sales Data, 1956-1958 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - City of Newburgh Bids and Financial Documents, 1970; 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - City of Newburgh Community Development Program Vouchers, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - City of Newburgh East Newburgh Renewal Project Survey and Planning, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - City of Newburgh Final Project Report: Application for Capital Grant, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - City of Newburgh Final Project Report: Application for Capital Grant 2, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - City of Newburgh Housing and Development Programs + NCDA, 1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - City of Newburgh in REM Proceedings, 1970-1973; 1976 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - City of Newburgh Lander Street Rehabilitation (Green), 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - City of Newburgh Lower Broadway Improvement Program, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - City of Newburgh Office of Econ Development Memorandum, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - City of Newburgh Parcel #18, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - City of Newburgh Part II Application for Capital Grant, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - City of Newburgh Urban Renewal 1955 to 1969, 1955-1969 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - City of Newburgh Urban Renewal 1970 to current, 1970-1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - City of Newburgh Workable Program, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - City of Newburgh, NY Rehabilitation of Delano-Hitch Swimming Pool, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Civil Service Data, 1967; 1969 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Clara Vandervoort Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Clarence J Klein, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Cleveland Best, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Close Out NYSUR 118, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Closing Notices City Assessor, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Closing Notices Insurance Agent, 1970; 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Closing Notices School Tax Office, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Closing Statements, Adjustments NYR 189, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Closings: City-Owned Properties, 1970-1974; 1975 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Code Enforcement, 1966; 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Code Enforcement Grant Application, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Commissioners of Appraisal System, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Community Development Agency City of Newburgh New York, 1977-1979 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Community Development Program, 1981-1983 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Community Development Program Bourne Apartments, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Community Workers Association, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Composite Program, 1971-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Condemnation Hearing, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Condemnation Orders and Litigation Summaries, 1971-1972; 1974-1977 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Conpat Realty Corp, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Consolidated Iron and Metal Co. Inc., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Construction Reproduction Cost, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 3)